With the 47th pick in the 2026 NFL
Draft, the Pittsburgh [music] Steelers
select
Jeremiah Bernard
Alabama
>> [music]
>> What has it been like getting to
Pittsburgh, heading over to the draft
theater with some other rookies and just
getting a taste of the fans here? It's
been It's been great.
Being able to be here,
meeting meeting all the coaches again
after being drafted.
It's a sigh of relief being able to come
in and you know be able to go and you
know have fun with the fans and you know
have my parents here with me. It is just
a great moment to enjoy. When the
Steelers traded up, were you thinking,
okay, call me, let me know what's
happening and did you expect this? No, I
didn't. But I didn't expect them to
trade up. I didn't even see that they
traded up. I just seen that
I just seen that they they had called me
and I was like, okay, I need to answer
this. It was like a spam risk number.
Usually I don't answer those, but I knew
I had to answer it today.
>> [laughter]
>> Do you remember that phone call? Do you
remember the moments afterwards of just
like taking it and knowing where you're
going to play football at?
>> No, yeah, no, for sure. I remember
everything. He called me and told me
like he was like, we traded up for you,
we're going to take you, can't wait to
have you. And then just being able to
you know go and hug my mom, my dad, you
know, I was crying like a little baby,
but
>> That's okay. [laughter]
>> No, for sure, but it was definitely a a
great feeling having everybody there to
support me. What does it mean to be
added to this wide receiver room with DK
Metcalf they just traded this off season
for Michael Pittman Jr. [music]
It means a lot.
It shows that you know that they value
me, they they trust and and believe what
I can bring to the table and how I can
have an impact to the offense.
They they trust that I can you know make
explosive plays.
And yeah, I mean I'm I'm just ready to
come in to learn from the older guys and
you know be able to you know help help
help the team succeed in whatever way
they need. You mentioned being excited
to come back here and see all the
coaches and staff again. You were here
for that pre-draft visit. What was the
biggest thing you took away from your
time with the Steelers organization
during that that visit? It just It just
really felt like home.
I know all the coaches were really
comforting me.
It was really like a personal
relationship you know when I was talking
to each of the coaches. And so like I
mean I felt really good when I was
leaving the visit. And like for them to
you know come back and get me it just
made it all like a full circle moment.
And in terms of Steelers fans, they can
Google your name, they can see your
highlights, all that. What do you want
fans to know about you, your work ethic
and what you will be bringing to this
team? Yeah, first and foremost I want
people to know and understand that you
know my identity is is in Christ and
that that's something that I believe in
the most and something that I want
people to you know see within me and you
know I want to bring that to the
community and have impact in any way I
can through that. And
I know I know that this organization is
going to get a selfless teammate, a guy
that's going to do everything he can to
help the team have success and win.
In terms of when you were in college, I
heard you got the nickname of Unc
because not just you know being older
but just how you carry yourself. Can you
elaborate on that just a little bit?
Yeah, I feel like
you know once once you get a little bit
older and you understand like you know
who you're living for and and what
you're trying to do things for,
you have a different perspective on life
and you carry yourself in a different
way and like a lot of people are not
used to seeing that. And so like that
that's kind of like where where that
come from just because I try to live a
different lifestyle than you know
you know people are used to. All right,
well welcome to Pittsburgh. Thanks for
your time. Thank you.